Hey, so five minutes.
BMW guys are bitching about break trouble.
Turn right back one minute.
Honey. We dropped down to seventh.
You can just overnight hopeful.
Sunrise catches just a break.
Holding up but go easy.
The crowds may have gone
but the racing continues.
Sunny Hayes ran the for
Geico racing Midnight shift
wheel likes to light up the night, but
with the BMW at the head of his pack,
he's got a massive job ahead of him.
Three. Moving up to the third place.
Don't want to me the just will
table let do this.
Any indication it appears
as though sunny hay.
See that that shot right boys, you get
back in that car, you need to do thing.
Up. Aren.
Hey, who's that lead? I'll kill you.
Hey.
I believe you forgot
something back's full chip.
Seriously your first win in Daytona.
Don't you even want to touch it? Come on.
Bad.
Luck. Bad luck.
Just touch it.
Yeah, will take that bonus check though.
So, so just hear me out. Look,
I want to bring you on board, your
CHR family now right here. Next year.
Let's run it back. We did it man.
Deal's the deal. I know what a deal is.
So that's it. One and done. I
appreciate the seat chip. I really do.
What kind of way is that?
The race you just spent your whole
life starting over man. Take care.
I'll see you down the road.
Hey, which one to watch? Got one.
Sorry. Can I use your phone for a
second please? It's not working.
No,
you know you remind me of this
friend I used to have. Which friend?
Friend who dressed better?
This is a goche suit. So's this,
huh? What do your friend do?
Drove cars. Was he
fast? A slow Did a wing?
Yeah he did.
Your son of a bitch. Oh, are you thinking?
Yeah. New day, new challenge. Exactly.
When I said to my son when I bought Aex GP
How deep in the hole
are you? I'll tell you,
but you have to promise
not to laugh. Shoot
350 million.
Don't laugh. Impressive. Well,
Ben, fun. Oh yeah, absolutely.
What's the problem then?
The problem is two seasons
and a half, zero points.
My best driver left for another
team except the car was a shit box.
The.
Team is your last place. My number two,
the rookie and the seasons have over,
lemme races left nine and we don't
turn it around. I lose the team.
But you own the team. No race wins.
In the first three seasons
the board can force a sales.
And it sounds like you need a new board.
Your driver.
You got to have two,
you got to have three.
You got a tyre assembly
line of kids raised on the.
Simulator. No, I don't have time for
some kids to learn how to come and tell.
I don't.
Well you don't just walk off
the street and pilot a rocket.
Yes you can if you've done it
before. That's the whole point.
Was 57 years old when he won the Monaco
Grand Prix? Who was who? Philipp.
56 years old. Google these names didn't
you? Some people look at Sonny Hayes.
They see a guy who lives in the van, a
gambling junkie who missed his shot. Wow.
Ruben, you are really s what? I
see a guy who makes teams better.
I see experience. I see knowhow. You
your my rookie is a phenomenal talent.
Phenomenal. But he's young. You
know what he likes maturity.
You plus him.
Boom. I got a team. Alright,
let's say I'm the next Louis Jean.
Him. The problem is it's not
just the driver, it's a car.
I followed your season. Ruben Shitbox
is being kind. I knew you were.
Watching. What if I told you we'd
get an upgrade package this weekend?
Six months in development.
Really? No. No. Wait,
I just need one of my cars across
the finish line. First one.
I love you. I'm not going back.
Okay. Okay.
What would he want you to do?
Join a boy band. Seriously.
Come on.
Seriously. I'd ask him
what he smiling about.
Come on. He's smiling at the possibility.
We both.
Know how that ended.
Yeah. Okay.
This is the first class
ticket to first class.
I'm offering you an open
seat in Formula one.
The only place you could
say for one day if you win,
you are the absolute best in the world.
Hey Ruben. Ever seen a miracle?
Not yet.
Me neither. Good, see you Migo.
Alright sweetie. Here you go.
Thank you. You're welcome.
Hey, let me ask you something close.
Friend of yours made you an offer
that was 100% positively too good
to be true. What do you do?
Well, how much are we talking?
Not about the money.
So what is it about.
One best one yet? Cough feels good.
Bring in Go distract one.
Boxy slab. Boxy slab.
Let's go find those Ments.
Sorry Julie,
try not to kill our driver.
What's the verdict? I don't know
what's happening. I mean it feels good.
I start to push then on the stairs and
the slow corners and no stairs to fast.
What on.
Entries? Exits.
Either. Both.
Great. Yeah.
Oh, there's 10,000 sensor on this thing
and you can't tell me what's going on.
But I'm not out there am I? So I am
going to need your help on this. Please.
Cook win.
He coming.
$150 Million Jungle. Jim.
So cute. We just let her
drive. Can't be any worse.
Joshua.
Hi Elizabeth here.
Oh yeah.
Doesn't matter. The press conference,
we want to steer around tech issues and
focus on the S strong bond with your new
teammate Luca Cortez.
Luca who I've known a week who only
was stir on the left at Red Board,
told the press he thought Joshua
Pierce was overrated. That Luca Cortez.
Yes.
Can't wait. All right, great.
Thank you. That's a yes. Yeah. Yes.
Sir. You right Ruben in big trouble.
He might have this on the team
knew. What does that mean for me?
Buyers is likely to
clean the house. Listen,
you need to show these people who
the number one driver really is, man.
How Well you're going
to lose your job. Yeah,
let that sink in.
We should be shooting.
Okay,
let's take the first half of the
season and raise it from our minds.
Someone says, Casper, what happened this
year? I swear the lives of my children,
I do not freaking know.
There's only this car and there is only
our future.
Who is that asshole? Wait a minute,
your man thought I was maintenance
sent me to the back gate.
Brother, you've never let me down.
Well there's still time.
AP GP. So Hayes, you race with
me back in the day against you.
You meet King McKenna,
our technical director,
Dutch do or Tiff mechanic
Linsky team principle.
You may know him by reputation.
Five time constructors
champion with Ferrari
as a real Jackman.
So is my pop. Can't win without him and.
I'm tell it the rookie Joshua,
why does he got a helmet? Safety?
Joshua, your city is safe. Okay,
son is here for the audition.
When was.
The last time you won a
race? Sunday. Daytona. Oh.
I'm sorry.
I meant Formula one. Oh,
I'm sorry. Then same as you.
Nevertheless say this. Has
anyone seen Luca Cortez.
When I interviewed with
you many little drivers?
Yeah, I all turned you down.
How many?
Seven.
That's a lot. I'm number seven.
You're eight.
This is a disaster.
Certainly you're more like a Technically
there is one who I've not heard from me
yet, but so I am a nine.
You know how numbers work right?
In business, my most
inspired ideas come late.
Yeah.
Best.
Things in life.
Usually write nights,
right? With respect. Ruben,
I cannot condone respect Our only test
they giving your long lost teammate and
audition.
Because by misunderstanding we're
not auditioning him. He's ing us.
That's your new driver. Good luck,
new wing, new side pods.
Any changes to the floor?
Not in the eight Other drivers
wouldn't have figured out.
That's why they call me Lucky number nine.
Listen, it's been a while since you've
driven that mate. You had a balance on.
These cars are tricky, so be
careful. Turn one and nine.
I don't want to see you get hurt.
How about we set a reasonable target?
Give me the same setup as him.
If I can't post a lap time
within a second of jps,
then I will promptly see myself out.
You're free to take a shot
at lucky number 10, 10.
10.
10. Who's jp?
Be careful on.
Okay, let's see what you got.
If he raised, he raised.
I used to be. Alright, put up Joshua.
Tony. Criticism is taxi. Make
it a hundred. You're on. Oh
sorry. This is Hugh Nickel or
race Ine. Good morning you.
How are my temps looking? Yep.
Almost one head to the left.
You should be good to push.
Right? You? Yes sir.
You should have taken that bet. Copy.
That.
Come on.
Wait, wait.
You okay? Yeah. All good?
Yeah, she's got a something.
Yeah, you mean had something.
But definitely snapping the high
speed corners. Unpredictable.
Delos had trouble with
the rears turns 14, 16 on.
The finals.
Turn maybe.
No, that's on me. Well what she left time.
He passed his entirely self-imposed
test by five hundreds of second.
Well it's start.
Bro.
We got nine races to catch the eye
of another team and as your manager I
have to advise you that we need to
start hitting these social and sponsor
events. You need more engagement
Josh Moore. Alright cool.
I'm just saying isn't
it? I'm starving. Nah,
go see someone though. Yeah. Hey,
take a picture off. Post that shit.
Send it to me. I'll post that shit. It's
my mom. Don't you dare post that shit.
I knew you was going to say.
Okay baby.
Yeah, just tired.
Bad tyres or the engine.
Come on mom. You don't
know about the cars.
Fiercely. Alright, I may not know much
about cars but I know a lot about you.
Go.
I might lose my seat. The team
not going to race anyways.
You are other teams.
Yeah, there's 20 seats
but they're all filled.
Plus there's this new guy and he's old.
How old?
Really old. Like 80.
He is such an asshole
Mom. He's quit though.
Don't mind that focus on you.
You can spend your whole life worrying
about other people but your time is right
now. You still love it.
Of course. I still love it.
And remember what your father used to say?
Put your head down and drive. Yes ma'am.
You kidding me?
Thought your job was to build
the fastest car on the planet.
My job is wind, so helps to feel it.
Mysterious moves at Apex GP who have
finally announced the driver who will take
their second seat. And in a bizarre twist,
it's American sunny Hayes who hasn't
raced in Formula one For over three
decades, son of an IndyCar mechanic,
Hayes was considered something
of a reckless young phenomenon.
The greatest who never was his former
career being brought to an abrupt halt
by horrific accident at
the Spanish Grand Prix.
He reappeared a decade later in racing
championships as diverse as Lamont,
nascar the Dakar rally and even a
stint as a New York taxi driver.
But now he's back racing for a team
which has in its entire F1 history never
even finished in the top 10.
None of this will dampen speculation that
majority shareholders of Anez capital
are looking to sell the
team and if they do,
that will likely also bring an end to
the career of F1 rookie Joshua Pierce.
Can.
We go now?
Desperate times they say
call for desperate measures,
but I honestly cannot recall a driver
signing quite as desperate as this
boy. Look at.
My son. That's the one.
That's the other driver.
Yeah, that's him and his stupid face.
But wait, you say he was
old. He not that old.
Hey Josh, you want the next shot
anywhere? Nine races means nine times.
You have to beat Chop Norris for now.
Start by winning over the press.
Yeah. You ready? Cool. Let's go.
That's a handsome man right there. Yeah.
Joshua. Hey, it's been an under an
opening, messy start to your season,
no wins,
car problems throughout and now
you have another new teammate.
How exactly are you finding them?
Messy start doesn't mean you can't finish
knee right Apex have a fire crew of
engineers. I'm confident we'll come
back. Five. In terms of new teammates,
I think it's really wonderful that Apex
are given second chances to the elderly.
Yes. Next question. Thank you. Yes, Don?
Mr. Hayes. Hi Don. Cav, welcome
back to the uk. It's been a while.
I mean last time you race at Silverston,
bill Clinton was your president
and we were all dancing.
The Macarena must be surreal to be back.
Yeah.
And during that decay you gave up
racing and gambled professionally
before declaring yourself
personally bankrupt. Yep.
You had a marriage and no and
two more ended in divorce. Yeah.
Anything you wish you'd
done differently? Yeah.
No more questions. Thank you.
For a bit per pie. Aviator
live casino or top slots.
Asan deposit this.
And before you.
Okay, here he comes. Apologise.
I apologise. I can't do that.
How you mean? Why not? Because it's a
sign of weakness. It's a sign of strength.
Sign of weakness.
Yeah. Dear, just do it Mom.
I.
Can't. You can you will.
Hey man.
A day at a press conference.
Stuff I said wasn't cool
so.
Basically what I'm trying to
say, I'm sorry. It's all right.
You're just worried I'm quicker
than you. Hi, I'm sunny.
Bernadette Pierce, nice to meet you.
Pleasure. It's all good.
I'll see you out there.
How you feeling? So good. Good.
You good, good, good.
No pressure.
Great.
Welcome. Along to Silverstone, the
circuit where on the 13th of May, 1950,
the formula one world championship began.
Today we kick off the final nine races
of this great championship season
here in the.
77Th British draw three as always,
11 tiers will take the grid fielding
two drivers each with race order
determined by the qualifying time set.
Yesterday will start
on followed by the and
two Ferrari.
Ruben.
Don't even talk to the moment,
just smile and shake hands.
He's an important member of the
board. Sonny, this is Peter,
one of my investors. Hi. He knows
absolutely nothing about racing but.
At least my eyes and ears on the
board and your Rubin's Hail Mary.
That is American football term,
right? The Hail Mary. The long shot.
I believe it's a religious
term. It is true. That is true.
I'm praying to them all. Yeah,
I'm the one guy on the board who
actually wants to keep the team.
The rest accordingly. Ants inferno.
But seriously man, I'm on the hook.
I've binged all of drive to survive.
I honestly don't think I've ever known
so much about ties is incredible.
I'm going to get back to my.
Why are.
Here first on the track.
Chance for the drivers to
warm up their tyres and.
Brakes. No,
there's a problem for Apex.
That's in P 22. It cars,
hang on, I got power
trouble. It's start mode,
sunny start mode on. Yes. So
lesson for everyone at home.
New car did read the manual.
It's been a while since he
was out on the track of this.
Race. He's not even going
to get into the race.
I got it.
If he falls too far behind
on the formation drink,
he'll be at risk of having
to start in the pit.
We're sunny. He's holding us up. Yeah,
just checking your truck. Just checking.
What's wrong with his car but
nothing with the plate Track ahead.
Hay has been able to push much harder
on this formation now he'll turn off at
the back of the grid
with warm ready to go.
Cheeky it's on.
What is this guy doing.
In your.
He's seven places since
has really struggled with this car.
They brought an upgrade
package this weekend.
Around this dirty air.
Can't position to attack.
He's complaining about his car over.
That's not what the team wants to hear.
Copy gap is 0.9 to dur within GRS range
should be able to take him on the next.
Train.
System to get, won't be
able to hold it up guys,
I got no grip. This is
trouble now for Apex G.
The Rebels tyres are now
warm and hasn't got his tyre
anymore. We've seen the attack
now it's all about defence.
All the attack pace is in
trouble. This could be.
The places
and it's damn this loose.
Tell me if you see.
A fixed, tell him to pull it back
the entry to get a better exit.
He thinks it's a, it's not.
20. Joshua appears struggling
out there at the moment.
Go get me off the go backwards.
Copy that 20 box box states
couldn't be hired for rookie Joshua,
this is not where you
want to be in last place.
Hit something. What was that?
Sit with the second pit stop.
Apex GP won't be happy with that taken
box copy to the bead box and
here comes sunny Hayes for a
fresh set of tyres.
You'll be hoping these will help
hold up to his current position.
P 15 Jack, Jack, not properly.
This is causing P in the A
go wrong is going wrong for this team.
So.
The pace man, tell him to let me
boss. Yeah. Position. Standby eight.
Josh is faster. Sunny's un coone tyres.
Yeah. Okay, so now fighting let through.
No fighting.
Who's fighting? I'm racing.
Trying.
To make you concrete up against
the old pit ball there Joshua.
You're going to have to fight for
position. You are a great honey. Hey fuck,
they're giving absolutely no
quarter, no benefit to their at.
They're win a but this is the battle.
Do.
No, this is mad.
The cardinal sin motoring double PN.
Just when it couldn't get any worse with
a black and gold. That's a tough one.
We can't corner.
We're bouncing around a place like we're
on the bloody tube and now we think
it's cool to leave will guns in the
pit box. Who even was that? That.
Was me of course.
Old man. You losing your hearing?
What.
Was that?
You want to do this here? Yeah. I'd love
to do this here in front of the team.
Right? The one that you apparently pulled.
Okay. You made a mistake. It happens.
I made a mistake. I love this
guy. Worry about it. Jody,
are you even listening to me? Not.
Really. No. Stop.
Josh is right and order is an order.
May I remind you that you report to me?
Cool. Just don't ask
me to give a position.
Sorry. Sorry guys.
Hold on.
You sw into a garage like some entitled
prick calling us piss porn and then you
drove like that. A swan.
Huh? You saw a swan. What's that mean?
You are an asshole. You come
in like an asshole. You swan.
So swans are assholes.
You are making a mistake of thinking that
I'm just going to be some grateful kid
who bend the knee to an old timer.
I can't mountain to get here bro.
Formula one.
Back home. We call that
a participation trophy.
Yeah. What the hell are
you smiling about man?
Did you win something?
There's 20 other drivers still out on
that track and you're in here posing for
that nonsense. Do you think
any of 'em respect us?
Do you They need to learn that no
one gets past us without a fight.
No one. You don't like
the way I'm driving?
Beat me. Swung.
Sorry I didn't see you.
Still beating yourself up.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know that one.
Thanks for what you said out there.
Just don't do it again. Okay. It
makes me look like I need help.
Oh man, you're right. Got it.
Hate from what it's worth.
Don't be shitty to yourself. It's plenty
people out there to do that for you.
Yeah.
I am sorry Ruben for demolishing not
one but both of your lovely cards for
coming back into your life.
Only to destroy it. Is this
your revenge for Monaco?
Yeah. I waited 30 years and came all
this way to humiliate myself on global
television.
Funny you think I brought you
in to make my other driver quit.
Listen, he's cocky, he's
arrogant. He's got a lot to learn.
You were talking, you were arrogant and.
You had a lot to learn. I'm not
here to hold anyone's hand here to.
Race. No you're not Holly. You're
here to give me a heart attack.
The board is up my ass and
I have to decide whether to continue
this fiasco or pull the plaque down.
You have till the end of the season by
which time Aex will be worth less than my
shoes. Sorry.
Tell me about Kate the car.
I want to talk to her about the car
world's first female tech director.
F1 team that takes balls.
Wow. Is that going to lie? She'll
see right through it. Not lying.
I'm sorry. Sorry she married. Okay,
stay there in that top of ice
until Budapest, you don't move.
Hey Ruben can't get there with this car.
Hey. Hey. Yeah, sorry. Hi.
Hi. What you working on?
I'm working on a new front wing concept
trying to pick us up a 10th or so.
Cool. And you can replicate
turns battery airflow.
No, just straight line drag. But I
mean we can calculate it from there.
Okay, what about turbulent air
from a car we're following?
No, not exactly but.
Track conditions, surface
quality, weather, ambient temps.
I'm sorry. Is there something
that you wanted to discuss?
Kate, you read my mind.
So Alan does want to get to be the
first female technical director of an F1
team. Let's take
dedication. Lots of hard work.
That's your urgent question.
Plenty.
Of people think I don't belong
here and happy dad you to the list.
If you're implying what I think there's.
A rule. I don't imply stuff.
So you like straight talk.
Stray arrow, no sugar.
Everyone thinks Reuben's lost it.
That he's clutching at straws.
They're saying maybe he lost
a bet ran over your dog.
They're saying Sonny
Hayes isn't a has been.
He's a never was.
Yeah, when I said I like straight
talk, I meant from others.
I mostly prefer praise flattery. Hero
worship at times straight up bullshit. Is.
That what Ruben's for?
Reuben. I love the guy
the most solid, steadfast.
So you asked if I was married.
Disloyal, mean, twisted,
bitter husk of a man.
Oh yeah.
And he also told me about big
string of ex-wives and girlfriends.
He said to avoid you like the plank.
Okay, let me explain this.
When you're going 200 miles
per hour into a rouge,
it's good to know it's got
your back. For the record,
in all my years in racing,
I have never ever hit on
the team technical director.
Well now that's a huge weight off my mind.
So what's this urgent question?
Okay, red Bull, Ferrari,
Mercedes, Aston, dun,
McLaren all have a speed on streamline
speed. Our shot is battling on the turns.
I need a way to chase
through the dirty air.
You want me to redesign
so you can follow closer?
We need to build our car for combat.
How am I supposed to make that safe?
You said anything not safe.
That's your question.
Yeah and here's the
straight talk. It's urgent.
I bet when you look in the
mirror you see this rough and
tumble old school, no bullshit.
Cowboy doesn't take orders,
goes his own way. Huh? Alone wolf.
Well I have news for you.
Formula one is a team sport.
It always was and maybe
that's why you failed at it.
The only question here is why
did so Hayes come back to F1?
Now that question is
extremely fucking urgent.
I'll start listening to
you when you finish a race.
After the Spanish Grand Prix.
The American rookie Sonny Hayes had just
signed a new contract and his future
looked very bright.
He'd earned a reputation for his
aggressive driving style seen by some as
reckless.
It nevertheless served him well as he
climbed up the order over the course of
the season relentlessly
pursuing his first F1 victory.
Hayes was running well in the opening
laps chasing down race leader ed and
Sena. However,
when Hayes made a risky move and attack
centre on the outside of a high speed
right hand turn, a frightening
scene unfolded as quick as a flash.
My goodness, I punch off the right
can see the memory on the right.
What on earth happened
there? I know this very.
I must say looks like
he really needs help.
There is nobody coming to at
the moment the flag is out.
Our models predict all teams are
going to be targeting a one-stop race.
Plan A is to switch from mediums
to hards between lab 27 and 33.
Plan B will be medium
hard medium first window,
16 to 21 second 45 to 51 plan C for soft.
Doesn't make sense. This temp
the tyre deck will be too high.
Matt Nelson. Yep. Yeah Joshua.
So we've just got to drive our race,
right? Let's not try and be heroes.
Let's make it through those
first turns. Clean. Can't win it.
Lap one starting at the back.
So we've just got to hope for
some lucky breaks later on, right?
Yeah.
Yeah. Create your own breaks. Hello. Hi.
I just said that.
Hope is not a strategy.
Anything else Professor.
Try.
Fast.
And here
with nowhere to go.
Check my toes. You've got Punctu right
and box. Box Slap first. Got that.
Turn a rule race
shit shoot.
Let.
Come in. Let's go. Let's go. Plant
C. No plant sees for soft tyres.
They won't last 10 laps in this heat.
No, that's a negative Sunny plan.
A is called plan A because when everything
is going right you see anything going
right. Plan C soft. It's not his core.
Tell him A as in asshole. Okay,
let's go soft.
What's.
Wrong with the car? The guy sitting in
it. Are you insane? We need hot tyres.
Everybody here is at a one stop race.
You see what everybody does? We lose
make go how you'll say that. Don't.
On.
My tyres I was a mechanic. Five champion
hands.
Tyres. Okay, let.
Be ready. Ready for what?
Where's Jayson currently running P 14.
Alright, here we go. Please make.
Move.
Any driver knows Magson will shut
the door on a clumsy move like that.
Glen Sea for chaos.
So that will bring out a safety
car which always shakes up a race,
slows down the leads the field together
and gives teeth the chance for a quick
pit stop which only costs
half the usual time.
Safety car we're box right standby.
Gate. Shouldn't we take advantage
while the safety guard window is open?
It's early. We gained track.
Position if we stay out.
Stay up, stay up. Watch you out.
B, wash Joshua. So the big
deal moves up for the moment.
Where's jp? Now Carly running P 12.
Okay, plan C. Be ready.
He's going to do it again.
Hayes is now down the lap. He has to.
Let BOTAs pass or face
a five second penalty.
Hayes is making it very difficult
for BOTAs under the rules.
He has to let him through before passing
three blue flags or risk of penalty.
Hey I'm just putting it out
there but maybe you should drive.
Sonny, you've got the blue flag.
Let bot us through. Come on now.
Little closer. Sonny do you copy?
I hear you through.
My bad.
That's going to bring
out another safety win.
2000 pounds. I think the team might
all start to start chipping in there.
Guys, it's another free stop. Please
tell me what box we are checking.
Keep maps. Stay out.
Stay out your stay out.
All drivers come in to take fresh
tyres but still mate on track.
He's moved up to B 11.
Look back.
I know, I know. Image.
What is he doing?
Think he dream scores a pint.
Tell JP to save his tyres Joshua,
just take care of your tyres. Okay
You have to make them last lost,
no sick a poopy.
Before to go in this stop and
go race. Thanks to Sunny Hayes,
the driver helped Moses as his teammate
now in 10 with a 12 second gap ahead
of strong. Tell JP.
To maintain that gap. Keep you
pushing. My tyres are gone man.
What are you waiting for? Copy
that. We have to call him.
He's losing over a second
Every lap. Standby.
Seriously, what are we waiting for?
Oopsie. Sorry guys.
That's the third safety car involved with
the a b driver bringing the Hungarian
North Creek to an absolute crawl. A sub
three second. Somebody keep beating.
Let's touch your box. Boss copy coming in.
What did you say? Finally gets bit A
on top 10.
The.
Yes.
You are crazy bro. It's just
10. What are you smiling about?
And behind our podium play six Hamilton
of pry complete the top five and kill
you.
Be as intense scoring expensive
for XGP their first ever
points.
Deals. Steel. I finished last.
Sounds great when you say it.
I know you have to go
see the Stewarts later.
What do you think they're going
to make of your race today?
Well I have to admit you guys got
this one right? I'm like update.
I'm still a bit rusty and finding my way
with this car but I'm confident we'll
get it.
A rope. Dope. It's Silverton a
demolition Darby here in Hungary.
You've been banned from casinos. Are
you trying to get banned from F1?
Take the whole team down
with you. Tell you what.
Don, when you say we make a bet
you're 10 pounds against my 10 grand.
We play some Mazda. I win your
10. We don't you wouldn't mind.
Let's do this man. Put your
money where your mouth is.
Why the hell I'll take that.
Okay, thank you so much.
Hey no more press.
No sorry you don't want to make the
media and you'll be fine. Take it.
Out of my paycheck.
We don't pay you enough up.
You know I have to say I kind of like it.
It's very punk rock for the brand.
Let's run it again.
How long has he been in that.
All day play with different
tyre pressures, ride heights.
Or his times.
He found half second.
Give me the same setup as him.
It must be like I'm seeing double.
Deal's. Deal ner for combat
at the Dutch Grand Prix you'll be
entering the tyres and corner at 322
kilometres per hour.
Yeah two legs Change my mind.
Yeah,
to answer your question,
I was in aerospace at Lockheed
when Ruben came in and he liked my
work, like my attitude.
He sold me on the thrill of fighting
to the death for 10th of a second,
travelling the world a roar of a crowd.
So I ran the idea past my husband
who swiftly became my ex-husband.
No.
Do you know what time it.
Is? Alright, tell me about the kid.
Okay, here's another one. My dad would
say slow is smooth. Smooth is fast.
For what it's worth. One more
time around. Just walk. Come on,
live on live with myself. If.
I can't keep up with
you Mr. 1990s, let's go.
Joining us today we have Casper
Smolinski, Zach Brown and Fred Vaser.
Now Casper,
can we start with you after what was a
fantastic result for the team in Hungary
last time out but Sonny has got
you skirting the line of penalties
and violations.
Is this your only strategy and have
you got any spare parts left in the
factory?
We compete like everybody else.
Race models change. We must adapt.
Well Zach, can we bring you in on
this because you faced haze before.
You know the grey areas in which he works.
Certainly do. First of all,
he's a lot grayer now and we keep
tabs on him back there behind us.
And Fred, any concerns from Ferrari?
What does Ferrari think of Apex?
We don't.
A better qualifying yesterday gets
us in the pick of things. P 10, P 15.
So we're going to go for a
two stop, medium, hard medium.
That's plan a final stitch.
We go hard for plan B so unless
do you have any track concerns?
Don't look at me, look at him.
It's good for jp. Start me on hearts.
Not the tracks cooled down.
You won't have any grip.
That's right for three weeks all
the talks been how reckless I am.
Everyone's wondering if I'm
going to drive him off track,
which means no one's going to
be watching out for him today.
You win us this race.
Meanwhile, Hayes is holding up the rest
of the pack stuck behind him in a DS
podium
way to go in this race and
potentially forecast anything happen.
Cars are coming.
In. Yep,
copy box Brooks is prepping a fresh
set tyres for haze that's going to
bring in all the other things
to avoid the changed my mind.
He's out the cars behind on tyres.
Apparently he doesn't
think he needs anymore.
Should we just do the
opposite of what he tells us.
To do? Stand by until I lose
my tyres. We how his tyres,
I think he means literally
Archer prayer coming in and there.
Goes tyres that's quite on the
track that will bring up the
virtual safety.
Car for a quick swing so the race gets
neutralised to everyone slows down to
40% of their racing speed and all the
race strategies will get a reset and that
is why this.
Is the perfect time to take a pit
stock When you're in the pit lane,
your opponents are restricted to a much
slower pace and you're not going to lose
as much track position when
you can joined. Take your
staying out, right Bobby,
Joshua, stay out. Stay out.
We want you out to gain
track position, copy.
Hay and.
He's.
Come out just in front of wax hay,
slow to midland, which will
cost red Ferrari precious time.
Push Joshua Bush. You want now be four.
Pork Who's coming out behind?
Let's see, let's go his.
Back. Yeah.
Closed up the front of the,
here comes. Let's see
and to.
Let's get trickier. Hey guys, what's
the plan? You're running P four.
We think P two and P three are switching
to winters for safety and it looks like
you want to stay. What do you want
to do? What's sunny going to do?
Take a wild guess.
Of staying out A and then
two Ferraris come in all way.
Intermediate tyres.
Their decides to play it.
Joshua P2.
So Joshua is staying out on slicks.
If you can hold on in find a dry line.
He's going to finish.
Second. Second. Not enough.
Okay, coming in for ick, not coming in.
How far behind me are they? 30 seconds.
Oh my god. He's going
to take out for step.
Let.
Me know when they hit
the main street. Don't.
Tell him Opinionize both cars. They
will take the win away. Trust me. Clear.
I'm pushing back. I can't catch him.
As the race leaders approach the
main straight is in another standoff
strategy.
Every he hangs on fraction
of a second. Joshua,
one last chance to catch
up. I see him almost.
Peter. Peter, follow me. Kobe, Joshua,
Sonny is your dog. I'm right behind him.
Come on, stay with, stay with me now.
Over overthink Joshua.
And now is it striking
distance? One L, jp,
wait for the straighter to turn one.
Be patient straight and turn one.
Joshua Sunny says wait for the
straight. The straight to turn one.
I'm right there.
For a bit per pie. Aviator,
live casino or top slots?
Za Asan deposit this.
Oh god sake.
How's he doing?
He's stable, he's resting.
Come on, very happy to hear
something. I'm so sorry.
What.
Happened? Sonny over here. Please
want to say Joshua said you're an asshole.
You got that track. I think
you're a dangerous asshole
Mrs. Pierce. You're part
of the same team, right?
Looking out for each other except you
had him doing something so dangerous.
It almost got him killed. Okay, listen.
No you listen to me. This is my son
and if anything, anything
else happens to him,
I'm coming after you and
you better hurry. I know.
Put you in a bed next to Joshua
for a very, very long time.
Do you think Joshua blame
you for what happened in.
Come on. It was clear that you
were running his race. Look,
you kept him out on slick tyres in
dangerous conditions that even if you told
him not to pass, wasn't the
accident inevitable? I may.
Joshua's back home recovering.
We are expecting to return in
a few weeks until that moment.
Our reserve driver Luca
about this right there.
We'll drive and next man up.
A chaotic week for Expensify Apex
GP and again it's sunny Hayes
at the centre. Many are
blaming him for his teammates.
Horrific accident at Monza.
His high stakes gambling style of
racing has the whole grid on edge and
while the controversy continues
over who was to blame?
Doctors have said that Pierce will miss
the next three races due to the burn
suffered on his hands as he
begins his road to recovery.
Today we're going with our combat upgrade.
The revised shapes will improve the flow
field under the floor allowing us to
run in dirty air with minimal loss.
Performance means we have to keep
the field close at all times and
that for this week's plan C.
Look,
they docked us to the back of the grid
because they don't like the way we drive.
Fine fuck 'em.
Because if we can pick up a 10th
of a second from you and from you
and you and me, if everyone in this
room can make one critical contribution,
that's a secondary lap and after 72 laps,
that's the difference
between last and first
plan C. Plan C is for combat.
Call back, call back,
call back,
call back back.
And.
Can't hang on. But this is,
it's I love.
Every race you miss fun. Just forget you.
So always seems to be one step ahead.
You live below Sonny may be
a Saturn, it may be a Saturn.
The upgrade has completely
changed this car.
And if Joshua is watching what
he must be thinking, what might
treat like a Josh? A be
a.
That's what up buys breakfast.
We back jp, we missed it.
Garage. I got a card just for the under
me.
We go.
It's a decent start and keeping it clean.
We go Ferrari ahead of here. The two AP
to work together as a team. It's a
welcome back to the track for Joshua P.
Hay to see him as they slice their weight.
Prepositions four and five on
ultimate Camel. Straight we go.
Now approaching top
speed, sunny Hayes, Josh,
he's showing effects from that crash.
The cars working beautifully.
They're working as a team.
Hang on to tail using the is he about to
try over into the C We go and wheel
desire rebuild Hayes and into the.
What is happening with this team,
their first race back together
and they ran into each other.
We pull that shit again. I
will knock your teeth out.
Oh no one gets passed us about a
fight, right? Oh, is this funny?
You think you've got a seat next year
because you just cut your chances in half.
That's how dumb.
You are. You failed. Why should
I listen to you anyway man?
Look man.
I don't give two shits about you.
You want to sabotage your career.
You go right ahead. I've seen hundreds
of guys with your talent come and go.
No one cares but you sabotaged
Ruben who backed you.
You sabotaged his team.
I won't let you do it.
Thanks coach. Get your
shit together. So stupid.
How'd you sum up your race today?
Oh it was good. The car feels great.
I think the team's done an amazing job.
It's just a shame of the contact
with Sonny. You hate to see that.
Hey. Hi, how are.
You? Good sensation.
What is the team brought
this by, gentlemen.
Brilliant. You made it. Come on down
Sonny. You know Joshua, Joshua, Sonny.
So I'm sure you both
the heard the rumours.
We all lose our jobs if you can't put
off a miracle and that's starting with
staying on bloody track.
We were doing just fine while JP was out.
I was out. I was listening to you ish.
Please don't call me jp. It's a.
Nickname. You don't get to choose
your name. Doesn't even make sense.
I says Sonny is a hazy.
We don't know do we.
Lads? Have I not delivered you a car
so you can do one thing
for me. Cards, come on.
I know you haven't yet. It's my team
meeting. We're going to do it my way.
We're playing poker. Yeah,
whoever wins gets to be our number one
driver tomorrow and if I win I get to
choose. Did he gamble for a living? Yeah,
now he's living in a van.
Takes us Holden.
Forward. Yeah.
So Sony here like straight
talk that right Sunny?
Yeah, that's what I hear.
So let's talk. Who wants to go first?
I'll go. I'll go first.
No, I'll go first. What's the difference
between Joshua Pierce and Sunny Hayes?
A lot of decades Hard one experience
of living in a van. Total freedom.
Total failure says the guy
still lives with his mom.
Says a guy with two pair
says the guy with trips.
Says the guy with a full house. Girl.
Wait, I don't even live with my mom,
okay, she just looks for me sometimes.
Did I need constructive criticism
for each other? What would it be?
Doug be such an a kid
that was constructive.
You have a deficient
frontal cortex. Oh what?
You can't analyse risk.
It's not all your fault,
it's not fully formed yet your age,
but come the day you learn patience
and stop being so mature. Thinking.
Patience is good. Patience Joshua.
He doesn't care about what anyone
else has to say about himself.
He just comes in and imposes his
will on one of us with no discussion.
He doesn't listen. I'm
trying but he doesn't listen.
Sony, what.
The.
Tool you have to play. My dad liked
to gamble. He made big bench too.
Put a big one on me.
How old were you? You
when your fathers died?
Sorry.
18.
Huh? Why do you raise.
Money, fame and free clothes.
Oh my god. With the phone. Put
the thing down. Will. Yeah.
What do you care what they say? Easy
for you to say they'll love you.
It's just noise man. Drive the car.
You're really good at it.
You might be great.
Hi. This is,
yeah, look at that.
Huh? Number one driver tomorrow.
Funding. Oh, this is nice.
You've got a go sponsor by
Omni G. Steal you uncle.
You're welcome to come with. Thank you.
I'm good. I a race tomorrow. Cool. Kate.
No thank you. Come on. Thanks
for this Kate. Come on back
girls. You might have, we're
going to go dancing. Dancing.
Listen, let's get this straight. Okay.
I don't mess around during the season
and never with a member of my team and
what I'm attracted to is winning
and you just lost a pair of fives.
Hey, you're a driver. Are you? Yeah.
Which.
Date? Apex gp. Can you
introduce me to Carlos sign?
I'll go get.
Why he say this place is weird. I
like this bro. Going to leave here.
I said I'm going to come just.
Bro.
Hey.
Oh shouldn't drink tequila.
Last time was Ruben's idea.
Yeah, the first part.
What?
Not the second.
Come on. Why are you here? Sunny? Huh?
I'm not much of a story.
Okay. I am here to prove everyone wrong.
My ex, my old boss,
my first year uni physics professor. That.
Bastard.
Yeah. And I'm telling we win. I haven't
so unfortunately I now rely on you.
That was going to be world
champion best there ever was
just a kid along the track with my idols.
Senator Manson Pros and I am quick,
I'm fearless. I was next
and then
it was all taken away.
Crash.
So asked my seat, my money, my sanity,
my self really became miss,
angry, resentful, shithead.
Not something I'm particularly proud of.
The one day I realised what I'd really
lost and it wasn't the titles or the
trophies or the records. It was
I love for racing
so I started driving.
Didn't matter the car,
the circuit didn't need anyone to watch.
As long as I was behind the wheel,
I was good.
Sometimes
come on.
It's rare but sometimes
there's this moment in
the car where everything goes quiet,
my heart beat slows.
It's peaceful and I can
see everything and no one,
no one can touch me.
I am chasing that moment
every time I get in the car.
I don't know when I'll find
it again but man, I want to,
I want because in that moment I'm.
Eight.
Ruben.
Where is he?
Who's who? What are you talking about
Ruben? Seriously. One. How dare you? Two.
I respect professional
boundaries and three.
Three. Yeah, he's on the balcony.
Well you're up early. Good dressed.
Yeah, what's.
Going on? They're coming for our car.
It's my duty to inform you that we've
received an anonymous tip that your
upgrade floor is in violation. From.
Who? I can't say, oh sir,
we submitted the drawings long
ago and you approved them all.
It's whether departures are racing with
were developed outside of your facility.
What? That's insane. Based
on the paperwork we've
received, there are concerns.
Hang on. Where'd you get? These
are internal documents. This.
Thing doesn't break any rules sir?
I'll say that when you can just, someone.
Can fabricate.
Documents your cars under
review. You know the procedure.
You cannot race unless you substitute
the previously approved components.
No. Do you mean our old design.
A.
Sheet box?
No. Where were you in the
last two years? Why not?
Because we might actually win a race.
Is that it? This is not car race.
This is like corporate as I'm
sorry. I'm sorry. Come here.
I'm talking to you sir, we the.
Upgrade. Were screwed.
Sonny. Let it go. Focus on a clean
start. We'll never win clean.
Can we just not break any rules? Yeah,
the rules are always against us though.
Aren't they?
Get them safe through lap one.
Sonny? We just need to
keep it in one piece. Okay.
Boy.
What the hell? I know what's
wrong with son Joshua. Yeah,
keep focus. You're so
good. What's she doing?
Not good. It's not good.
Sunny, when you take this time,
these tyres last, take it easy.
Oh.
He's put the in qualified mode.
He's going to run the battery to
put it back mode. What's going on?
What's happening?
Why do either this?
What's wrong with Tanya's or golf?
We don't leave.
C five. Neck fracture, spinal condition,
compressed thoracic
vertebra. Further blunt.
Force in pet trauma likely to
result in vision loss paralysis.
Death deaf
really leading with the
good news, don't they?
This is a report from 30 years
ago. Why didn't you tell me
you never struck have raced again. So
how do you think I'd feel
if you die on the truck
revenge from Monica? It's not a joke.
It's made. Who's liable? Sunny. I
don't think there's some bullshit.
Put hot to get you out of this. No
remember drivers, we're not drivers.
Not anymore. I'm sorry,
we're not. We're losers.
We're a pair of dumb sentimental
broke losers.
Okay, you're off the team.
You're vanishing the garage with all.
I never should forward you
into this honey. I'm sorry.
You can wait.
I need this.
No one drives forever.
Sunny. Not even you.
Pepper load up Monza just like it happened
in the rain.
Run again. Please
run again please.
Sunny. Hey you're not Abu Dhabi.
I fly out tonight. Yeah,
I wanted to catch you.
So listen,
we both know that the boards wanted
to unload Apex from the start,
but yeah, then you brought into town,
raised our whole profile and
now I've got buyers lining
up. Got to be honest with you man,
I thought you were going to be
the final nail in the coffin,
but now I see the play and I
want you as part of the package,
what sort of package?
I've set up a sale where I run the
team and keep you on for strategy,
maybe even team principle
with the money from that deal.
I can make you a very rich man.
Here's the thing with the changing in
regulations, new Mercedes Power Unit,
Kate's arrow, two new drivers.
We've got a real shot of the
championship next year. What about Ruben?
Don't worry, we won't embarrass him.
We'll keep him on with a title
or brand ambassador. Something
I get final say don't change
a thing. Do what you do man.
And that's the irony here.
The board originally approved your hire
because we thought you would help us
lose. Sorry to make you sweat. Hey
that's my number taught your people. But
right after the race I want to lock
down the deal. Okay? So by Sunday,
perfect. Listen this
thing can be your legacy.
An F1 champion what you
always wanted, right?
It was you for those
documents wasn't it? Huh?
You're a killer man.
I am. I'm a winner on you. Huh?
Okay. Oh hey,
how's the back better?
I've got an amazing guy.
I'll hook you up. Hey Mary.
You good?
Listen mom, I got to tell you something.
In Monzo right before the crash
it was my decision to make a move.
So I didn't tell.
Emily. I've been working
the phones with IndyCar.
I think I can get you a test drive bro.
They're trying to pull in a
new demographic obviously.
And the ladies that love that smile
I throwing some incentives like
flights and cars.
Listen, cash, you can go.
I don't need you today. Oh
mate, you've got media next.
I don't care. They could find me besides,
that's not why I'm doing it,
right Josh? Starting tomorrow.
We're not doing it anywhere.
It's all just noise.
Media engagement, followers. Listen,
I've got to focus on
the race Auntie, please.
Will you hurt the man?
Yo. Hey. Hi. Hey.
Guys, what's happening? Park family
waiting for FIA to cut the seals.
Oh good. We got time then. For what?
For?
No, no.
Welcome to the palette club.
For our most valued guests,
please grab a drink,
make yourselves at home and
enjoy the very best view there is
of Formula one.
Hey Jesus, it's like a mortar around here.
How you get here. Premium economy.
What is this?
Well that's my bullshit
loophole. I don't forget it.
I'm not even going to read that.
That is a real legal document from a
real Tijuana lawyer WA all li ability to
you and your company vis-a-vis
this race. Myself and me. And
since you owe me my last paycheck,
technically I'm still on this team.
Kate, where's the shit box?
The FIA confirmed that the documents
were forged and they were sent by someone
from Apex.
I don't care about your loophole.
I don't. That is my car.
You are not raising it.
Really? No, Sonny is it?
I can't let you do that. I can't.
Okay, the last thing I
do is drive that car.
I will take that life man.
A thousand times.
We can't win. We can if we don't try.
How come you never look at a card?
What card?
Welcome to the very final spots
on the grid and as ever will go
here in P 22 because we're
here in the Apex. GP team.
The late stage driver
switch. That's your guy,
isn't it being replaced by Hayes
who didn't even make the trip to.
You. Got my phone.
Good luck to about you too James.
Hey Sunny. Hey look,
I know we brought out different team but
look this is your last yes half far and
thought.
What's that?
Bloody hell. Bloody hell.
All set for our season finale here in
away we Joshua
position as we.
Inside.
And three days out
before Hazel. Feel that.
Game guys we're alive.
I hope he hasn't damaged the car but
despite everything it's still a great,
it's.
P 16 PS P nine
Mercedes Ferrari holding onto
the lead eight in the big field.
Let's see if they can do
anything to shake up this race.
Get leader 16 seconds.
Keep JP plus 20 seconds.
Plus 20 Alexis pit though you know why.
It's a busy race for Sunny Hayes.
And now here comes Kevin Anderson
looking to make a move and this.
There's history between the two.
Often the era hot force
meets the I object looking
at inside and hits hay.
Coming in
slow is smooth, smooth
it's fast. Here we go.
Hey, exit the fence. He had to come
in because of that damage to his tyre.
Thought of Joshua Pierce.
Where do a GP go with
guys?
Chaos. Copy that. Joshua slows
down the metre for Sunny.
So does ING for him.
Strategy this season
position for now only got
to keep these tyres alive.
It's the only way we keep this close
and then we need luck. Aren't we ahead.
Here?
Lap 25 and every driver so far is
Pit Paul one and he leads the race.
Joshua Fierce.
Controlling the pace out in front and
that gives his teammate Hayes a chance to
maintain his position in the midfield.
Despite the contact puncture and pit.
They're working really well
together. What we doing up there?
He's keeping the leaders at bay.
DRS academic.
Straight sunny, got it
onto the back straight.
He's enjoying this new
upgrade and he's, he's got.
Sonny, you have got the pace. Keep pushing
despite, but that moment is nearly over.
Snap up the inside and
he's through. Fabulous.
First in from Joshua Pierce. Max
is passed and his down there.
Here comes it's overtake trucks
now to P three guys. My
tyres shot. Copy that box.
JP box.
Box Pierce stretching those tyres to the
and he exits. The he'll
have pressure ties.
Now attack in second of the race Sonny.
The three leaders are still on the hard.
They're going to have to stop
again. This is the pit window.
What are the leaders going to undercut?
I need to beat there when they do
need three.
Ferrari ppa. Could he beat it to one?
Depends on their stop.
5.8 he needs to pick up half a second.
So you need half a second go.
So Hayes is on the charge track
Ra through the first corner.
So Hayes, it's really tight.
So Hayes is ahead
down the inside,
there's a chance sight and he
takes it and he looks up the
Ferrari goes away and says
thank you very much indeed.
Stage.
Are close to the league.
They're working together.
Two big cars in the top 10, but still a.
Long way to go. 20 laps remaining.
Eight has worked their way up the order.
We're now at the final pit stop window.
This our chance for P one.
Make sure JP beats 'em up.
Hamilton and Le Claire come into
the pit. Look here. Stays out.
Tuck to me. Can I catch him? Yeah, they're
just coming out. Push now. Push now.
Push. Push. Copy, push it.
Oh this is going to be Joshua
second this, let's go.
Joshua
will have a hard time holding him
on with Hamilton and on Fresh tyres.
Four out to go Sunny haters in P four.
He's five seconds behind his teammate,
but both through all tyres. There's
little chance they'll gain any places now.
And here's Hamilton Attack
appears in the turn five.
And he's through. Nobody has to stop
again on our tyres in nine laps over.
Nuclear attacks and passes.
Pierce his tyres absolutely finished.
There's nothing you can do about that.
I'm sorry.
Guys of got nothing been left.
There's been the apex
cheap story all year long.
Plenty of risks are great.
Underdog story, but we don't.
Need talent. Crowns a champion,
those grip tyres are gone. Yeah,
sadly the deck's been stacked against
them and now they're out of cards to play.
It ain't over, right?
No, but nothing can change. It's
the worst. Failing in the world.
That's a big one.
All over the racetrack. And
substantial damage to the barriers.
The stewards have no choice but
to red flag this race miracle.
And speaking of damage, Martin.
He's won to be allowed
to continue in this race.
If we could get his car all the way around
the circuit and back to the pit lane.
Sonny. Sonny, can you get it back?
I'll get it back. I'll get it back.
I have to push him back.
He still going? He's
still going. Jp. Red flag.
Red flag. Come in. We're
still alive. Armando.
Red flag.
And somehow Sunny Hayes has got his
car back to the pit lane Sun. I know,
I know. Never seen one.
Free Good girl. Let's go. New shops,
both cars race the tyre
pressure for three quick.
Laps.
Car red flag horses. The
teams can make changes,
they can make repairs to their
cars, but only in that pen lane.
And with only 10 minutes to make
repairs. He makes GP has their.
Work cut out and all cars
can fit a fresh set of tyres
for the three Sprint. Dad. Dad,
we going to make it? I don't know.
That was clean. That wasn't mean.
Not this time. Not this time.
Tell that to the stewards.
Check the replay. I got this.
I'm good. Good, good, good.
What the stewards will be looking at
is whether Hayes went off completely or
kept at least one tyre on track during
the contact with Russell. Yo, you good?
Yeah. Good. Listen, you
are on track and it was.
Your corner P three and P four.
Let's go. Cuban Hayes reputation.
They'll be looking at this
really, really closely.
I'm not expecting a quick decision.
Come on. That's clearly a.
Penalty. Not that that's what we want,
but objectively that's the guy.
I glad it can't end this way. He.
Has the timeout like the last 30 years.
It's in the hands of the racing God
stuff. Going to believe. God believe.
Plenty going on here in the pit. Oh.
Here comes the new wing.
This is a massive job. Yeah,
but will the car hold together
for the remaining three hours?
Blood. Mario looks okay now the
marshals just sweeping the mastery.
Bits of debris off the track and
the club continues to take down.
Yes, just over two minutes until
this race gets underway again.
Three laps. Three laps is a
lifetime. Go win this thing.
Hey sunny, sunny. You got a minute?
We got you a car. Oh.
You broke. Thank you.
Because Apex GP didn't
make the top 10 in qualify,
they have a new set of soft tyres
available which will give them X speed
over the cars ahead of them,
of the used soft tyres.
This red flag is a lifeline. You'd
almost wonder if Stanley didn't engineer.
It,
but we are the only cars on fresh tyres
because we sucked in qualify yesterday.
Never got the chance to use them.
Sometimes when you lose, you win.
That don't make sense.
It's.
A Sony thing.
Second formation of the evening when this
is going to be Hamilton.
Sonny, we just heard from
the stewards. God damn it.
Now we're debating whether
to tell you. Casper.
Says yes, but Kate says don't. She
says you're fast when you're angry.
Tell her job well done.
And here's news.
Stewards have made their decision that
lap 55 collision between Hazen Russell
is ruled a racing incident investigation.
That was your line. Sunny
can finish your race.
Joshua still got two cars
in the mix. Then we've got.
A team. Once those red lights go out,
this will be an absolute
sprint to the finish position.
Advantage to Mercedes and Ferrari,
our entire advantage to Apex.
Kill jp. To follow my lead,
Joshua says to follow him.
He's behind me.
Lost it with me.
He's giving you a
get it.
Racing. It's a beautiful
sight. But now their.
Hamilton. Yeah.
Why didn't they overtake? Lewis will
defend whichever car attacks first.
The boat can't work. Yes.
Someone has to sacrifice.
Come on guys. Talk to me West.
Can he finish one more lap? JP
Hamilton never backs down. Yes,
the race man. Yes, he's on track.
What you do fights your be one.
No more risks.
Sonny Bush be one. You be one. Apex.
GP has only won lap to go. The
question is do they have the car?
We have the driver.
What's up? He's.
It means another three
years for Ruben, right?
Yeah.
I guess we'll check back about that deal.
Presuming.
You are still on the board.
Breathtaking.
Breath. Incredible. What this.
It's a for the ages. An absolute thrill.
And this man his been 30 years.
I'm going to win a million races.
You should at least that one.
We did it.
If you somewhere nowhere to find thanks.
I'm happy.
Where I am. Delicious.
Yeah, baby.
Another right? I don't know about.
Somewhere that beats this.
I wanted to say see you down the road,
but in a way that was more poetic.
So can I see you down the road?
Yes.
Hang on to that. Okay.
And drive fast.
Now. Where do you think you'll
go? Don't worry about me.
Go celebrate.
But you're off to where you know
a couple more dragons to slay.
It's your team now.
It was always my team.
I'll be watching. See you around. Sw.
Hello?
I told you're looking for
a driver. What's your name?
Sonny Hayes.
Have.
You ever driven?
Nope. We can't pay much.
Not about the money.
So what is it about I.